paygear.com 2013-05-19

# Privacy - Shopping Cart | Affiliate Software | Sell Online

Privacy Policy  
---  
  
PayGear is one of the most trusted names in the e-commerce industry and respects the privacy of our partners, clients and their customers. Any and all information collected through our system is treated with the utmost care.

**PAYGEAR PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Protecting your data is very important to us. We would like to ensure that you have a pleasant experience using PayGear. That's why we have implemented security and privacy regulations that are binding for our company and affiliated companies to ensure the best possible protection for your data when you make purchases through PayGear.

PayGear asks customers to supply various personal data when placing an order, such as name, e-mail address, address, and credit-card information. We use this data only for the purpose of filling an order, or communicating with the customer or supplier about the status of an order.

PayGear will release personally identifiable information to third parties and organizations when we believe it is appropriate for us to do so in order to comply with the law or to protect against fraud. We will also release such information to cooperate with law enforcement or other governmental investigations (without necessarily requiring the requesting law enforcement or government agency to formally serve us with a subpoena), comply with all valid court orders or subpoenas, protect the legal rights of us and our users, or when we believe it is needed for fraud protection and/or credit risk reduction.   
Except for the circumstances set forth in the above paragraph, we will not knowingly distribute customer information to be used by any third parties. 

**LINKS**

Our Web sites contain references (links) to third-party Web sites. Data collected on third-party Web sites are subject to the third-party's privacy regulations. We are not responsible for complying with the third-party's privacy regulations, nor are we responsible for handling this data. Customers who make their information accessible to a third party should read the third party's privacy statement.

**COOKIES**

"Cookies" are small data files that are temporarily stored in a designated file in your browser. Cookies allow you to experience faster and more pleasant experience. PayGear’s cookies are used only to identify the customer, not to identify any specific customer traits. These cookies do not store sensitive data. 

**SECURITY**

Because PayGear accept sensitive information from end-users such as passwords and credit card numbers, we site uses SSL. This logic encrypts the data being sent to the server from the browser using high-level encryption technology. Once the data is received from customers it may be required that the data be maintained for a certain period of time inside our private network. Encrypting the data means it cannot be viewed in plain text. 

**ELECTRONIC NEWSLETTERS**

You have the option of receiving advertisements or marketing related information from our Web site or our company by activating a check box displayed during signing up for PayGear. You can opt-out of this service at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link that is included at the end of each advertising e-mail. You will automatically be unsubscribed from this service and will receive no further messages.

**DATA SHARING**

We will share your personal data only with our affiliated and associated companies directly involved in order processing, as well as with the product vendor. These persons are legally and/or contractually obligated to use this data only for the purposes of reviewing and performing contracts and providing technical support, if offered by the vendor. Use of the data beyond these parameters is not permitted. 

We assure you that we will not share, sell, or rent your personal data to third parties, unless

1\. we have obtained your express written consent, or 

2\. we are legally obligated to share this information. This may be necessary for investigations into abuses of our services, or for general legal action. In these cases, personal data will be made available to prosecuting authorities and, if necessary, to injured third parties. This also applies if the user relationship has been terminated. However, we will only share this information if we are provided with justified and documented indication of abuse of our services. 

**PRIVACY REGULATION CHANGES**

To keep up with the rapid development of the Internet, our privacy regulations need to be adjusted from time to time. You will find information about any changes here. By continuing to use our services, you agree to accept the changes to our privacy regulations. 

If you have questions, suggestions, or comments concerning data privacy, please send an e-mail to the company with the contact link below.
